Hey Jude
Hey Jude don′t make it bad
Take a sad song and make it better
Remember to let her into your heart
Then you can start to make it better
Hey Jude don′t be afraid
You were made to go out and get her
The minute you let her under your skin
Then you begin to make it better
And anytime you feel the pain,
hey Jude refrain
Don′t carry the world
upon your shoulders
For well you know that It is
a fool who plays it cool
By making his world a le colder
Nah nah nah nah nah nah nah nah nah
Hey Jude don′t let me down
You have found her now go and get her
Remember to let her into your heart
Then you can start to make it better
So let it out and let it
in hey Jude begin
You are waiting for someone
to perform with
And don′t you know that It is just
you hey Jude you′ll do
The movement you need
is on your shoulder
Nah nah nah nah nah nah
nah nah nah yeah
Hey Jude don′t make it bad
Take a sad song and make it better
Remember to let her under your skin
Then you′ll begin to make it
Better better better better
better better oh yeah
Nah nah nah nah nah nah,
nah nah nah hey Jude